<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="action_showcase">View Tutorial</string>
    <string name="showcase_main_title">What is SOLA Open Tenure ?</string>
    <string name="showcase_main_message">\n \n
        									\n Open Tenure is an open source software app, developed by UN-FAO, for the in-the-field community based recording of land rights.
											\n The boundaries of a land use right can be mapped and land use and land user details can be captured as
                                            \n well as images of supporting documents and photos of the land use.
											\n Open Tenure is used with an instance of the web-based SOLA Community Server where previously
                                            \n captured land use recordings and map imagery can be downloaded before field capture and new land use recordings can be uploaded after field capture.

     </string>
    <string name="showcase_claim_title">Recording Details</string>
    <string name="showcase_news_message">\n \n
        									The News Tab give you access to the FAO web site page describing the SOLA suite of opensource tenure software (including Open Tenure)
                                         \n
                                         \n </string>

    <string name="showcase_map_message">\n \n The Community Map tab gives you access to the Open Tenure Map Viewer

    </string>
    <string name="showcase_persons_message">\n \n The List of Recordings tab gives you access to ??
        									 Shows the contact details of the representative of the land user providing the details captured in Open Tenure
        									\n \n
        									 Select one row of the list to edit the contact details about the representative or land user
                                            \n including ID details and photo if appropriate
											\n \n ....or....
    </string>
    <string name="showcase_claims_message">\n The List of Recordings tab displays a list of land use recordings that have been downloaded or recorded on your device along with their status
                                           \n \n Status Types:
                                           \n   •   L - Lodged
                                           \n   •   U - Uploaded / Not Validated
                                           \n   •   C - Challenged
                                           \n   •   M - Validated
                                           \n   •   R - Rejected
                                           \n   •   W - Withdrawn
    </string>
    <string name="showcase_claim_select_message"> \n \n \n
        										 Select a recording from the list to view or edit its details and map the extents of the land use
 										      \n \n Use the blue Arrow Icon to upload a recording to your Community Server
										      \n \n Use the red X Icon to remove a recording from the list on your device
    </string>

    <string name="showcase_claim_message"> \n Describe a land use recording by entering details through a series of tabs
                                           \n The first 6 tabs are fixed format tabs for describing standard land use characterics.
                                           \n Up to 2 additional tabs can be added that are dynamic to record land use characteristics for extra fields of specific interest to a community.
                                           \n These fields are defined using the SOLA Web Admin application.
                                           \n \n The Recording Tab has these fields:
                                           \n* "Land name" being the name the locality of the land use being recorded  is commonly known as
                                           \n* "Recording type" being the category of land use being recording
                                           \n* "Land Use" being the primary land use of the area being recorded
                                           \n* "Date land use began" being the date the land use began in this location
                                           \n* "Notes" being any additional details considered appropriate by the Community Recorder
                                           \n \n At the bottom of the form are two buttons:
                                           \n* "Add (or Modify) Contact" to record the land user representative providing the details and their contact details
                                           \n* "Select Recording to Challenge" in the case of a land use recording that is disputed and a challenge has been recorded. This allows that challenge to be linked to a previous land use recording
     </string>

    <string name="showcase_claim_map_message">\n \n Allows you to define the extents of a land use recording using the map imagery as the base map for a reference
                                             and, where necessary, the GPS position from the mobile device\'s built-in GPS.
                                        	  \n \n Once all land use extents have been defined, a (snapshot) map of the land use recording can be generated and automatically added as a supporting document to the land use recording
    </string>

    <string name="showcase_claim_mapdraw_message">\n \n A Long Press on the map creates a new land use boundaryResponse corner
        										  \n \n A (light) Tap on a land use boundaryResponse corner puts that boundaryResponse corner in Edit Mode
                                                  \n Edit Mode operations are:
                                                  \n* the white X icon deletes the selected boundaryResponse corner
                                                  \n* the white Compass icon provides precise spatial editing.Arrows in each cardinal direction display.
                                                  \n Use these arrows for precise definition of boundaryResponse corners and then the white Dot icon when boundaryResponse corner is satisfactorily defined
                                                  \n* the white Circle with a Diagonal icon exits Edit Mode
                                           		  \n \n Long press on an existing marker to drag it around
                                                  \n \n Open Tenure can snap to existing boundaryResponse corners or onto existing boundaryResponse lines
    </string>
    <string name="showcase_claim_document_message">\n \n \n
        										  Displays a list of documents attached to the land use recording
         										   \n \n
         										  A document can be selected from the list to view its details
                                                  \n The red X icon deletes the document from the land use recording



    </string>
    <string name="showcase_claim_documentAttach_message">\n \n \n
        										  The Paperclip icon allows you to attach an existing file that has previously been stored on your device
        										   \n \n
        										  The Camera icon activates the camera on your device so that you can take a photo and for that image
                                                  /n to be attached to the land use recording



    </string>

    <string name="showcase_claim_adjacencies_message">\n \n \n
        										  Record a brief description of adjacent lands according to their location relative to the land use being recorded (ie north, south, east and west)
         										   \n \n
         										  Where there are adjacent land use recordings made by Open Tenure, these recordings will automatically be displayed as adjacent.



    </string>

    <string name="showcase_claim_challenges_message">\n \n \n
        										  Displays a list of any challenges made against this land use recording
                                                  \n \n To look at the details of a challenge, note the name of the challenged land use recording or the land user contact person
                                                  and search for it using one of those names in the List of Recordings tab

    </string>

    <string name="showcase_claim_shares_message">
        										  Lists the land user right shares applying to a land use recording (normally a single 100% share)
         										   \n Open Tenure initially assumes a single (100 percent) share in the name of the land user representative and this
                                                    is what will be what is initially seen in this list. This simple 100 percent share arrangement MUST be modified using the following mechanisms:

         										  \n A share can be selected from the list to look at the land user(s) associated with that share and to change the land user details or add further land users to the share
                              \n
                              \n OR (the most usual situation) to ADD a new Group to record the name of the family using the land AND delete the land user representative (as the sole land user in their own right)
                              \n

												  \n The counter control allows the percentage associated with the share to be changed

                                                  \n The red X icon allows a share to be deleted

												  \n The green + icon allows you to add a new share to record a more complex land user arrangement for the land use recording

                                                  \n Open Tenure will not allow you to record a share arrangement that does not total 100 percent


    </string>
    <string name="showcase_actionNews_message"> \n \n The White Triangle enclosing an exclamation mark icon displays when Open Tenure is run for the first time. This function must be used then to initialise Open Tenure for use with your Community Server
                                                \n \n The Logon icon gives you access to the Community Server once you have entered your user name and password (obtained from your system administrator)
                                                \n \n The Lock icon encrypts the data captured using Open Tenure for when this data is submitted by email
        										\n \n The List icon gives access to:
        										\n• "Settings" to define the url values and map layer for your SOLA Community Server, Geoserver (map imagery) and survey form
												    \n
                            \n•  "View Tutorial" to re-visit this tutorial

    </string>
    <string name="showcase_actionMap_message"> \n Community Map tab Icons:
                                               \n* the File Download icon only displays when you are zoomed in at near maximum scale and starts the download of map imagery tiles
                                               \n from the Geoserver imagery for the area currently displayed in the Open Tenure map viewer
                                               \n* the Logon icon to display logon form (you must first register as a user on the Community Server)
                                               \n* the (folded) Map icon centres the Open Tenure map display on the community\'s defined area of interest
                                               \n* the Bulls-Eye target icon centres the Open Tenure map display on your current location
        								  	   \n* the cloud Download icon starts the download of land use recording details from the Community Server for the area currently
                                               \n  displayed in the Open Tenure map viewer
        									   \n* the List icon allows you to specify the Open Tenure base map layer options available PLUS the actions associated with any icons that cannot be displayed on screens of smaller devices
    </string>
    <string name="showcase_actionPersons_message"> \n Click on the + icon to add a new person or group and record the applicable details:
                                                \n \n Person
                                                \n* "First name" (mandatory) - record first names
                                                \n* "Last name" (mandatory) - family name
                                                \n* "Date of birth" (mandatory) - use date control or enter manually in format YYYY-MM-DD
                                                \n* "Gender" (mandatory)
                                                \n* "ID Type " select value from list
                                                \n* "ID Number" record from ID document
                                                \n* "Postal Address"
                                                \n* "Email Address" - this email address is where automated messages concerning the property claim will be sent
                                                \n* "Mobile phone number"
                                                \n* "Contact phone number"
                                                \n \n Group
                                                \n* "First name" (mandatory) - name of the group
                                                \n* "Date of Establishment" (mandatory) - use date control or enter manually in format YYYY-MM-DD
                                                \n* "ID Number" - may not exist but for legally recognised entities, like companies, record their registration number
                                                \n* "Postal Address"
                                                \n* "Email Address" - this email address is where automated messages concerning the property claim will be sent
                                                \n* "Mobile phone number"
                                                \n* "Contact phone number"


    </string>
    <string name="showcase_actionClaims_message"> \n \n The Flag Person icon to create a new land use recording
                                                  \n \n The Logon icon to display the logon form that will then allow you to upload and download completed land use recordings
                                                  \n \n The List icon gives access to:
                                                  \n• "Settings" to define the url values, map layers for your Community Server (including map imagery in addition to GoogleEarth) and to activate a language not recognized by Android such as Burmese and Albanian.
                                                  \n
                                                  \n•  "View Tutorial" to re-visit this tutorial
                                                  \n•  "Backup local data" being the land use recordings data recorded on your device
    </string>

    <string name="showcase_actionClaimDetails_message"> \n \n  The Save icon saves all data describing this recording
                                                        \n \n  The Export icon creates a compressed zip file of the recording (to be sent as email to the community secretary
                                                        \n responsible for the operation of your Community Server) once the land use has been completely recorded and saved
        												                        \n \n  The Print icon creates a summary of the land use recording details
                                                        \n once the land use recording has been mapped and land use and land user details has been saved.
                                                        \n \n The List icon contains a menu option of View Tutorial to re-visit this tutorial
</string>
    <string name="showcase_actionClaimMap_message"> \n \n  The wrench icon allows you to switch between different map editing modes such as: measuring the distance between land use boundaryResponse markers or adding markers to the main boundaryResponse, adding
                                                     markers which are not part of the main boundaryResponse.
         											\n \n  The green + icon creates a new boundaryResponse corner at the current position as determined by the device\'s built-in GPS.
                                                     Because of the accuracy constraints of the built-in GPS, this land use boundaryResponse point should be repositioned (use a Long Press action on the map display)
                                                     relative to the map imagery if the boundaryResponse point position is clear on the map imagery. In such situations, Open Tenure records both
                                                    the GPS position and the map imagery position of the boundaryResponse point.
                                                    \n \n The white Rotate icon rotates the map and displays the device\'s compass. To stop the Rotate function, use the
                                                      white Circle with a Diagonal icon. A two finger swirl motion will also rotate the map. Useful for in-the-field orientation
        										    \n  The Bullseye Target icon centres the map on your current position (as determined by built-in GPS)
        										    \n \n  The Camera/device icon generates a map snapshot based on the current map display and automatically attaches this as a supporting
                                                     document to the land use recording. In the case of a previous map being stored as a supporting document it replaces the older map.
    </string>


    <string name="showcase_actionAlert1_message"> \n \n  You must now initialize the application.

    </string>
    <string name="showcase_actionAlert_message"> \n   This icon initialises Open Tenure by configuring it for use with your communitys SOLA Community Server.
                                                  \n  When you need to connect to the community server for your community you will need to clear any
                                                  \n Open Tenure data on your device, change the url settings for the community server and re-initialise.
                                                  \n \n  These steps are:
                                                  \n  1) Using Android Settings - Apps - Open Tenure. Click on the Clear data button
                                                  \n  2) Change the url values in Settings menu option available from the List of Recordings tab on the initial main Open Tenure screen
                                                  \n  3) Click on the white Triangle icon to (re) Initialise Open Tenure (available from the News Tab on the initial main Open Tenure form)
    </string>

    <string name="showcase_end_message">\n \n
        									..and now..
											\n \n Please try using Open Tenure. If you have any suggestions or you come across any issues
                                            \n please contact us (npullar@gmail.com)
											\n\n You can view this tutorial again at any time selecting "View Tutorial" from the List - View Tutorial menu option.
     </string>


    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>

</resources>
