<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="action_showcase">View Tutorial</string>
    <string name="showcase_main_title">What is SOLA Open Tenure ?</string>
    <string name="showcase_main_message">\n \n 
        									\n Open Tenure is an open source software app, developed by UN-FAO, for the in-the-field recording of property rights.
											\n The boundaries of a property can be mapped and property and ownership details can be captured as well as images of
                                            \n supporting documents and photos of the property.
											\n Open Tenure is used with a web based community server (such as SOLA Community Server) where existing property details
                                            \n and map imagery can be downloaded before field capture and new details can be uploaded after field capture.

     </string>
    <string name="showcase_claim_title">Claim Details</string>
    <string name="showcase_news_message">\n \n 
        									The News Tab give you access to the FAO test SOLA Community Server web site where you can review uploaded property
                                         \n details captured using Open Tenure.
                                         \n It also provides access to the FLOSS SOLA Open Source Software Community web site where you can find out more about
                                         \n SOLA open source software solutions</string>
    
    <string name="showcase_map_message">\n \n The Community Map Tab gives you access to the Open Tenure map viewer
                                        
    </string>
    <string name="showcase_persons_message">\n
        									 Shows the list of persons making the claim on behalf of others or themselves
        									\n \n
        									 Select one element of the list to edit details about the person  
                                            \n including  name, date of birth, gender, ID details and photo
											\n \n ....or.... 
    </string>
    <string name="showcase_claims_message">\n The List of Claims Tab displays a list of property claims that have been downloaded or recorded on your device along with their status
                                           \n \n Status Types:
                                           \n   •   L - Lodged
                                           \n   •   U - Uploaded/Unmoderated
                                           \n   *   C - Challenged
                                           \n   •   M - Moderated
                                           \n   •   R - Rejected
                                           \n   •   W - Withdrawn
    </string>
    <string name="showcase_claim_select_message"> \n \n \n
        										 Select a claim from the list to view or edit its details and map the property
 										      \n \n Use the blue Arrow Icon to upload a claim to the Community Server
										      \n \n Use the red X Icon to remove a claim from the list locally
    </string>
    
    <string name="showcase_claim_message"> \n Describe a property claim by entering details through a series of tabs
                                           \n The first 6 tabs are fixed format tabs for describing LADM/STDM characterics.
                                           \n The last 2 tabs are dynamic and the contents of these tabs are defined using the SOLA Web Admin application.
                                           \n \n The Claim Tab has these fields:
                                           \n* "Claim name" being the name or identifier that the property is commonly known as
                                           \n* "Claim type" being the (LADM or SOLA extenstion) primary right for the property
                                           \n* "Land Use" being the (SOLA extension) current primary land use for the property
                                           \n* "Date claim applies from" being the date the primary right was first known to exist
                                           \n* "Notes" being any additional details considered appropriate by the Community Recorder
                                           \n \n At the bottom of the form are two buttons:
                                           \n* "Add (or Modify) Claimant" to record the owner(s) of the property
                                           \n* "Select Claim to Challenge" in the case of a property claim that is disputed and a challenge has been recorded. This allows that challenge to be linked to a previous property claim
     </string>
    
    <string name="showcase_claim_map_message">\n \n Allows you to define the boundaries of the property claim using the map imagery as the base map for a reference
                                             and, where necessary, the GPS position from the mobile device\'s built-in GPS.
                                        	  \n \n Once all the boundaries have been defined, a map of the property claim can be generated and added as a supporting document to the property claim
    </string>
    
    <string name="showcase_claim_mapdraw_message">\n \n A Long Press on the map creates a new boundary corner
        										  \n \n A (light) Tap on a boundary corner puts that boundary corner in Edit Mode
                                                  \n Edit Mode operations are:
                                                  \n* the white X icon deletes the selected boundary corner
                                                  \n* the white Compass icon provides precise spatial editing.Arrows in each cardinal direction display.
                                                  \n Use these arrows for precise definition of boundary corners and then the white Dot icon when boundary corner is satisfactorily defined
                                                  \n* the white Circle with a Diagonal icon exits Edit Mode
                                           		  \n \n Long press on an existing marker to drag it around
                                                  \n \n Open Tenure can snap to existing boundary corners or onto existing boundary lines
    </string>
    <string name="showcase_claim_document_message">\n \n \n 
        										  Displays a list of documents attached to the property claim
         										   \n \n 
         										  A document can be selected from the list to view its details
                                                  \n The red X icon deletes the document from the property claim
         										    
        										 
        	                                        
    </string>
    <string name="showcase_claim_documentAttach_message">\n \n \n 
        										  The Paperclip icon allows you to attach an existing file that has previously been stored on your device
        										   \n \n
        										  The Camera icon activates the camera on your device so that you can take a photo and for that image
                                                  /n to be attached to the property claim
        										    
         										  
        	                                        
    </string>
    
    <string name="showcase_claim_adjacencies_message">\n \n \n 
        										  Record the owner or property name of adjacent properties according to their location relative
                                                  \n to the property claim being recorded (ie north, south, east and west)
         										   \n \n 
         										  Where there are adjacient property claims recorded by Open Tenure, these property claims will automatically be displayed as adjacent.
         										  
        										 
        	                                        
    </string>
    
    <string name="showcase_claim_challenges_message">\n \n \n 
        										  Displays a list of any challenges made against this property claim
                                                  \n \n To look at the details of a challenge, note the name of the challenged property or the claimant
                                                  and search for it using one of those names in the List of Claims tab
        										    
    </string>
    
    <string name="showcase_claim_shares_message">
        										  Lists the ownership shares recorded for the property claim
         										   \n (Open Tenure assumes a simple (100 percent) ownership in the name of the claimant and this
                                                    is what will be initially seen in this list. This simple 100 percent share arrangement can be modified using the following mechanisms)
                                                    
         										  \n A share can be selected from the list to look at the owner(s) associated with that share and to change the owner details or add
                                                  further owners for the share
                                                  
												  \n The counter control allows the percentage associated with the share to be changed
                                                  
                                                  \n The red X icon allows a share to be deleted
                                
												  \n The green + icon allows you to add a new share to record a more complex ownership arrangement for the property claim
                                                  
                                                  \n Open Tenure will not allow you to record an ownership share arrangement that does not total 100 percent
        										 
        	                                        
    </string>
    <string name="showcase_actionNews_message"> \n \n The White Triangle enclosing an exclamation mark icon displays when Open Tenure is run for the first time. This function
                                                \n must be used then to initialise Open Tenure for use with a particular Community Server
                                                \n \n The Logon icon gives you access to the Community Server once you have entered your user name and password
                                                \n (obtained by registering on the Community Server website)
                                                \n \n The Lock icon encrypts the data captured using Open Tenure for when this data is submitted by email
        										\n \n The List icon gives access to:
        										\n• "Settings" to define the url values and map layer for the Community Server, Geoserver (map imagery) and survey form
												\n•  "View Tutorial" to re-visit this tutorial
           
    </string>
    <string name="showcase_actionMap_message"> \n Community Map Tab Icons:
                                               \n* the File Download icon only displays when you are zoomed in at near maximum scale and starts the download of map imagery tiles
                                               \n from the Geoserver imagery for the area currently displayed in the Open Tenure map viewer
                                               \n* the Logon icon to display logon form (you must first register as a user on the Community Server)
                                               \n* the (folded) Map icon centres the Open Tenure map display on the community\'s defined area of interest
                                               \n* the Bulls-Eye target icon centres the Open Tenure map display on your current location
        								  	   \n* the cloud Download icon starts the download of property claims details from the Community Server for the area currently
                                               \n  displayed in the Open Tenure map viewer
        									   \n* the List icon presents the Open Tenure base map layer options available for selection
    </string>
    <string name="showcase_actionPersons_message"> \n Click on the + icon to add a new person or group and record the applicable details:
                                                \n \n Person
                                                \n* "First name" (mandatory) - record first names
                                                \n* "Last name" (mandatory) - family name
                                                \n* "Date of birth" (mandatory) - use date control or enter manually in format YYYY-MM-DD
                                                \n* "Gender" (mandatory)
                                                \n* "ID Type " select value from list
                                                \n* "ID Number" record from ID document
                                                \n* "Postal Address"
                                                \n* "Email Address" - this email address is where automated messages concerning the property claim will be sent
                                                \n* "Mobile phone number"
                                                \n* "Contact phone number"
                                                \n \n Group
                                                \n* "First name" (mandatory) - name of the group
                                                \n* "Date of Establishment" (mandatory) - use date control or enter manually in format YYYY-MM-DD
                                                \n* "ID Number" - may not exisit but for legally recognised entities, like companies, record their registration number
                                                \n* "Postal Address"
                                                \n* "Email Address" - this email address is where automated messages concerning the property claim will be sent
                                                \n* "Mobile phone number"
                                                \n* "Contact phone number"
                                                
                                                
    </string>
    <string name="showcase_actionClaims_message"> \n \n The Flag Person icon to record a new property claim
                                                  \n \n The Logon icon to display the logon form that will then allow you to upload completed property claims
                                                  \n \n The List icon gives access to:
                                                  \n• "Settings" to define the url values and map layer for the Community Server, Geoserver (map imagery) and survey form
                                                  \n•  "View Tutorial" to re-visit this tutorial
                                                  \n•  "Backup local data" to backup property claim data recorded on your device
    </string>
    
    <string name="showcase_actionClaimDetails_message"> \n \n  The Save icon saves all data describing this claim
                                                        \n \n  The Export icon creates a compressed zip file of the claim (for emailing to the community server)
                                                        \n once the property claim has been completely recorded and saved
        												\n \n  The Print icon creates a summary of the property claim details
                                                        \n once property claim has been mapped and property claim has been saved.
                                                        \n \n The List icon contains a menu option of View Tutorial to re-visit this tutorial
</string>
    <string name="showcase_actionClaimMap_message"> \n \n  The wrench icon allows you to switch between different map editing modes such as: adding markers to the main boundary, adding
                                                     markers which are not part of the main boundary or measuring the distance between markers.
         											\n \n  The green + icon creates a new boundary corner at the current position as determined by the device\'s built-in GPS.
                                                     Because of the accuracy constraints of the built-in GPS, this boundary corner should be repositioned (use a Long Press action on the map display)
                                                     relative to the map imagery if the boundary position is clear on the map imagery. In such situations, Open Tenure records both
                                                    the GPS position and the map imagery position.
                                                    \n \n The white Rotate icon rotates the map and displays the device\'s compass. To stop the Rotate function, use the
                                                      white Circle with a Diagonal icon. A two finger swirl motion will also rotate the map. Useful for in-the-field orientation
        										    \n  The Bullseye Target icon centres the map on your current position (as determined by built-in GPS)
        										    \n \n  The Device icon generates a map based on the current map display and automatically attaches this as a supporting
                                                     document to the property claim. In the case of a previous map being stored as a supporting document it replaces the older map.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="showcase_actionAlert1_message"> \n \n  You must now initialize the application.
        
    </string>
    <string name="showcase_actionAlert_message"> \n   This icon initialises Open Tenure by configuring it for use with the test SOLA Community Server.
                                                  \n  When you need to connect to the community server for your community you will need to clear any
                                                  \n Open Tenure data on your device, change the url settings for the community server and re-initialise.
                                                  \n \n  These steps are:
                                                  \n  1) Using Android Settings - Apps - Open Tenure. Click on the Clear data button
                                                  \n  2) Change the url values in Settings menu option available from the List of Claims Tab on the initial main Open Tenure form
                                                  \n  3) Use the Triangle icon to (re) Initialise Open Tenure (available from the News Tab on the initial main Open Tenure form)
    </string>
    
    <string name="showcase_end_message">\n \n 
        									..and now..
											\n \n Please try using Open Tenure. If you have any suggestions or you come across any issues
                                            \n please contact us (neil.pullar@fao.org)
											\n\n You can view this tutorial again at any time selecting "View Tutorial" from the List - View Tutorial menu option.
     </string>
    
    
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    
</resources>